<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spokane and Miami Real Estate Video Blog with John Graham</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Legacy Group Network is to be your best resource for Spokane and Miami real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Legacy Group Network, your professional Spokane and Miami Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:43:39 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:43:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What's the Best Place to Live in Spokane?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NaZgWZhyCzQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring is nearly here and we are very excited for all the activity that the season will bring. There are some very exciting things going on in Spokane, for both buyers and sellers, and we want you to know about them. People have been asking us where the best places to live in Spokane are, so today we are going to talk about a few of our favorites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;post-cta&quot;&gt;
Buying a home? &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Click here to perform a full home search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Selling a home? &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Click here for a FREE Home Price Evaluation &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=There are some very exciting things going on in Spokane, for both buyers and sellers, and we want you to know about them.%20http://localhost:4000/spokane-real-estate-agent-buyer.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“There are some very exciting things going on in Spokane, for both buyers and sellers, and we want you to know about them.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first is Kendall Yards, located downtown, right on the Spokane River. It’s beautiful down there, and the area is within walking distance of downtown. They’ve got condos, single-family homes, restaurants, shopping, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second place we love in Spokane is Coyote Rock at River Crest. It’s down on the Spokane River in the valley, and it’s a beautiful neighborhood. Located right on the Centennial Trail, you can walk right out your front door onto the trail, or onto the river. We think this is the next big thing in Spokane real estate, and we think you’ll agree once you see the properties there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to check out some of these hotspots and see what they are all about, we are here to help, just give us a call or send us an email. We’d love to set up a time with you to show you just how great these areas are.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 12:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spokane-real-estate-agent-buyer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/spokane-real-estate-agent-buyer.html</guid>
        
        <category>Spokane Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Spokane Hotspots</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Spokane Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Should You Prepare Your Home for Sale?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6BXoyc4H99E?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new year is here and before you know it, the spring selling season will be here. Today we are going to talk about how we prepare our sellers to put their homes on the market in the spring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing we want to talk about is having your mindset ready to sell your home. A lot of sellers are emotionally involved in their home, so selling is a big decision. What you really need to focus on is that the home is not a family member, but a building and a business investment. You have to do whatever it takes to cash in on that investment, and being too emotional can hurt that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=In Coeur d'Alene and Spokane, nobody has a better track record than The Legacy Group%20http://localhost:4000/legacy-group-real-estate-home-sell.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“In Coeur d’Alene and Spokane, nobody has a better track record than The Legacy Group”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, you want to hire the right agent. The best way to find the right agent is by looking at
their track record of success. In Couer d’Alene and Spokane, nobody has a better track record than The Legacy Group. We have sold more homes in the last 5 years than anybody else in the inland northwest and sold over 350 just this last year. We have the systems in place that allow us to do things other agents can’t, and sell your home much faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, pricing your home correctly is a big step. There is a school of thought out there that pricing your home high initially will eventually bring you the most money for your home sale. In reality, that’s not the truth. We have found, through our track record of success, if you price a home correctly at first, it allows us to negotiate more aggressively on your behalf to get you that full price offer you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d like to thank everyone for checking out our blog today. We truly appreciate your business and staying in touch with us. If you have any questions for us at all, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us a quick email today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 16:15:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/legacy-group-real-estate-home-sell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/legacy-group-real-estate-home-sell.html</guid>
        
        <category>Spokane Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using a Full-service Team Guarantees You a Better Real Estate Experience</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/I3rxSbxK95Q?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Hire the Legacy Group to Buy or Sell Your Home&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When making one of the largest financial decisions of your life, doesn’t it make sense to hire a team with a proven track record of success?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team has a perfect record. In fact, we’ve been the #1 team in the Inland Northwest for the past six years in a row! We sold 327 homes last year, and over 1,500 in the past six years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re so confident in our abilities that we have a Guaranteed Sale program. Meaning if we don’t sell your home, we’ll buy it from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our buyers, we have our Love It or Leave It Guarantee. If you’re unhappy with your new home in the first 6 months after moving in, we’ll sell it for you for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to buy, sell, or invest in real estate in Spokane, Coeur d’Alene, or Northern Idaho, please don’t hesitate to contact us and our team of real estate professionals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 11:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spokane-real-estate-legacy-group-why.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/spokane-real-estate-legacy-group-why.html</guid>
        
        <category>Why Hire Me</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
